Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1949-2010
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
- Series 5: Audiovisual materials, 1970-2007 (Boxes 721-739)
  - Subseries 5.3: Other audiovisual formats and VHS tapes, circa 1973-2007
    - Inherit the Wind Copy 2, Side 1 audiocassette, circa 1973 (Box 739)
    - Inherit the Wind, Copy 2 Side 1 and Side 2 audiocassette, circa 1973 (Box 739)
    - Inherit the Wind, Day 2 Side 1 and Side 2 audiocassette, circa 1973 (Box 739)
    - Inherit the Wind, Day 2 Side 3 and Side 4 audiocassette, circa 1973 (Box 739)
    - Inherit the Wind, Day 2 Side 5 and Side 6 audiocassette, circa 1973 (Box 739)
    - Inherit the Wind, Day 2 Side 7 and Side 8 audiocassette, circa 1973 (Box 739)
    - Inherit the Wind, Day 3 Side 1 and Side 2 audiocassette, circa 1973 (Box 739)